Norman Zolot Papers 1991.0003
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Legal Case files, 1940s, 1950s, 1960s, 1970s, 1980; 41.3 Linear feet
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, maps, notes, photographs, publications, sketches (preliminary), 1974-1980; 1.3 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_30)
    Subjects include: Case files #1979.28-#1979.50: A. Fiorillo Company, I.B.T. Local 677; Amalgamated Industrial Union Local 76B, University of New Haven; B.N. Beard Company, I.B.T. Local 677; County School Service, I.B.T. Local 677; Dewey Shorter v. Chicago Bridge & Iron Company; First National Supermarkets Incorporated, I.B.T. Local 559; Hartford Despatch & Warehouse Company Incorporated, I.B.T. Local 671; I.B.T. Local 443, United Liquors Limited of Connecticut; I.B.T. Local 671, Ensworth; Labor Realty v. Anthony Giuliano et al; Lewis & Elizabeth Corvo; Maurice Saucier; McLaughlin Ford Incorporated, I.B.T. Local 677; The Nestle Company, Bakery & Confectionery Workers Local 50; Philip Peeler; Pisano, Pascale, Cirillo; Robinson Consumer Products, I.B.T. Local 677; Standard Knapp Incorporated v. I.A.M. Local 782; Stone & Webster Engineering Corporation v. Iron Workers Local 15; Uniform Services Incorporated, I.B.T. Local 667.
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, notes, publications, sketches (blueprints), transcripts, 1970-1980; 1.3 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_31)
    Subjects include: Case files #1979.51-#1979.68: Baskin & Robbins Incorporated, I.B.T. Local 677; Cooper Marketing Association, Brewery and Soft Drink Workers, I.B.T. Local 1040; Edward P. Conroy v. The Union Labor Life Insurance Company, et al; H.L. Bruneau Trucking, I.B.T. Local 443; I.B.E.W. Local 420, John Madigosky, Connecticut Light & Power Company; I.B.E.W. Local 457, Trombley By-Pass, Connecticut Light & Power Company; I.B.T. Local 191, Wilson Freight-Strickland Transportation; I.B.T. Local 671, Connecticut Natural Gas Corporation; James Furlong, et al v. Printers Local 150; Joseph W. Nadwairski v. Connecticut Light & Power Company, I.B.E.W. Local 457; Lego Systems Incorporated, I.B.T. Local 671; Lehigh Oil Company, I.B.T. Local 493; Parts Warehouse Incorporated, I.B.T. Local 671; Pervel Industries Incorporated v. Connecticut Commission on Human Rights and Opportunites, et al; Walter Brown; William Ogden, et al v. Spector Freight Systems, et al.
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, notes, publications, transcripts, 1965-1974; 0.5 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_32)
    Subjects include: Case files #8.1-#8.9: Hall-Brooke Hospital; I.A.M. Local 1396, Atlantic Wire Company; I.B.T. Local 145, Brock Hall Dairy Company; I.B.T. Local 145, City of Stamford; I.B.T. Local 145, Connecticut Limousine Incorporated; I.B.T. Local 145, United Liquors Limited; Sheet Metal Workers Local 40 v. Capitol Ventilating Company.
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, legal documents, notes, publications, 1966-1974, 1976; 0.5 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_33)
    Subjects include: Case files #8.10-#8.15: Fournier v. Ford; Frito-Lay Incorporated v. Teamsters; Hall-Brooke Hospital Foundation Incorporated v. I.B.T. Local 145, et al; Hildreth Press Incorporated v. Local 401, International Printing Pressmens and Assistants Union; The New Haven Typographical Union v. Ro Mark Typographical Company Incorporated, et al; Sheet Metal Workers' International Association Local 40, Robert M. Schneider; The Spencer Turbine Company v. Sheet Metal Workers' International Association Local 570.
- Series II: New England Teamster's Pension Fund, 1968-1978; 0.75 Linear feet
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, notes, publications, transcripts, 1968-1977; 0.5 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_34)
    Subjects include: New England Teamsters Pension Fund.
  - Administrative records, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, notes, 1968-1978; 0.25 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_35)
- Series III: United Aircraft Corporation and the International Aerospace Machinists, District 91 Case files, 1958-1960, 1963-1971; 3.6 Linear feet
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, legal documents, notes, publications, transcripts, 1958-1960, 1963-1971; 1.3 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_36)
    Subjects include: International Association of Machinists District 91, United Aircraft Corporation, U.A.C. v. I.A.M.
  - Legal documents, transcripts, 1968-1969; 1.3 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_37)
    Subjects include: International Association of Machinists District 91, Superior Court, United Aircraft Corporation, U.A.C. v. I.A.M.
  - legal documents, transcripts, 1968; 0.5 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_38)
  - Legal documents, transcripts, 1968; 0.5 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_39)
- Series IV: Case files, 1949-1968, 1971; 1.8 Linear feet
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, notes, publications, 1949-1967; 1.3 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_40)
    Subjects include: Other case files: A.I.W. Local 100, Tubular Products, Vacation Pay Arbitration; Alurn, Intercity Coach Company; Bridgeport Brass, Accounting; Bura, Mary v. New Haven Waist & Dress Company; Butler, Victor and Quality Studio; Chadwick Construction Company, Operating Engineers Local 478; Connecticut Light & Power, I.B.E.W. Local 1226, Willimantic, Arbitration; Connecticut Light & Power, Contract; Dinkoski, Mr. & Mrs. Walter; Eaton Truck Rental Company, Incorporated; Elmwood Upholstering; Federal Labor Union No. 20705, Dextone Suit; Gherlone v. Purificato, Superior Court; Gherlone, Louis; I.A.M. Lodge 1335, Vickers Incorporated; I.B.E.W. Local 468, Hartford Electric Light Company; I.B.T. Local 191 v. Drinkwater Sons, Incorporated; I.B.T. Local 443, Coca Cola Bottling Company of New Haven Incorporated; I.B.T. Local 677 v. Gallagher; Kalaski, Victor v. Burnside Motors; Kuritch, Esther v. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union, Local 217, et al; LeClerc, Adelard, Estate of; Mallozzi v. Mallozzi; Meatcutters 371, Grand Central Markets; Metal Trades Council of New London; Mid-City Truck Company, Incorporated; Morrow v. Bradley Semiconductor Corporation; Nelson, Raymond v. White, James; New Britain, City of and Local 992, International Association of Firefighters; Operating Engineers Local 478, Ley Construction; Ruoppolo v. Petro; Sikorsky Local 1150, United Aircraft Company, Agreement.
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, legal documents, notes, publications, 1955, 1957, 1960-1968, 1971; 0.5 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_41)
    Subjects include: Other case files: Sikorsky Local 1150, United Aircraft Company, Agreement; Shindler, I.L.G.W.U. Closing, 4 Morris Road, East Haven; Swift & Company, Teamsters' Local 443; Trelli, David v. I.B.T. 677.
- Series V: Labor reference files, 1944-1953, 1974; 4.9 Linear feet
  - Administrative records, correspondence, clippings, financial records, notes, publications, 1945-1949; 1.3 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_42)
    Subjects include: Reading files #1-#7: Connecticut Department of Labor Monthly Bulletin, Connecticut Housing,Connecticut Income Tax, Connecticut Legislative Materials, Income Tax (Accounting Problems), Income Tax Publications, State and Federal Printed Materials, Tax Study Commission, Tax Study Report, Unemployment Compensation.
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, fliers, legal documents, notes, maps, publications, 1944-1950, 1974; 1.3 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_43)
    Subjects include: Reading files #8-#12 and others: Americans for Democratic Action, membership and sympathizers; Arcudi, John; Connecticut State Industrial Union Council, Press Release; Disability Unemployment; Family Budget; The Governer's Committtee on Full Employment, The Connecticut Economy; The H.O. Canfield Company v. United Construction Workers et al, H.O. Canfield Brief; Interstate Conference on Non-Occupational Disability Benefits Program; Labor Literature, U.S. Supreme Court, Bethlehem Steel Company v. New York State Relations Board, Taft-Hartley material, American Federation of Labor; New York Income Tax; Workmen's Compensation, Connecticut; Workmen's Compensation, New York State.
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, financial records, fliers, legal documents, notes, publications, 1945, 1947-1953, 1974; 1.3 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_44)
    Subjects include: Reading files: Labor Literature, The Taft-Hartley Act: Questions and Answers; Legislation; Legislative Bills; Mediation; Minimum wage and hours; Rates and classifications, Jenkins Bros. and General Electric, Bridgeport; Sickness and Disability Insurance; State of Connecticut State Tax Department, Sales and Use Division; State Delegates to the Connecticut Democratic Convention; Tax information; Temporary Disability.
  - Administrative records, clippings, correspondence, legal documents, notes, publications, 1946-1952; 0.5 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_45)
    Subjects include: Reading files: Temporary Disability (California, Insurance Report, Massachusetts, New Jersey, New York, Railroad, Rhode Island).
  - Administrative records, clippings, financial records, legal documents, publications, 1948-1953; 0.5 Linear feet Folders with labeled tabs (Box 1991.0003_46)
    Subjects include: Reading files: Unemployment Compensation; United States Department of Labor, printed materials; Workmen's Compensation; Zolot, Norman and Arcudi, John, How to Read Financial Statements, Connecticut Federation of Labor.